[Thuds]
[Growling noises]
[Thud]
This is yates,
I need harbor patrol.
What the hell?
Good God.
- Stowaways?
- Yeah. Looks like.
Yeah,
but what happened to 'em?
[Growling]
[Roars]
[Screaming and growling]
[Tearing, slashing sounds]
[Creature's snarl echoes]
[Grunts]
Huh.
- [Growls]
- [Grunts]
[Fighting sounds]
[Object shatters]
[Growls]
You are the Grimm.
You have the coins.
Give them to me.
- You killed my parents!
- Ugh!
[Yelling and grunting]
Why'd you kill 'em?
[Grunting]
[Grunts]
You find
what you're looking for?
[Hisses, grunts]
Nick.
Nicky.
It's me.
Mom?
[Growls]
[Breathing hard]
There once was a man
who lived a life so strange,
it had to be true.
[Tense music]
Only he could see
what no one else can...
the darkness inside,
the real monster within.
And he's the one
who must stop them.
This is his calling.
This is his duty.
This is the life of a Grimm.
♪ ♪
[Growls]
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.Com
How?
I have to
take care of him first.
He's one of the men
that killed your father.
With what I put into him,
he won't be out long.
[Grunts]
We have to make sure he was
sent by the dragon's tongue.
[Grunts]
You could see him
for what he is?
Yes.
[Police siren blares]
All right,
they're looking for you.
You're gonna have...
- hey.
- Kimura's in there.
We got an officer down
on the porch.
Yeah, we know,
paramedics are on their way.
You okay?
Yeah.
He's alive.
- Should we turn him?
- Yeah.
You shoot him?
No.
He's got a wound here.
You stab him?
It must have happened
during the fight.
Cuff him.
I don't give a damn
about his wound.
I don't want him
hurting anybody else.
Sorry we didn't
get here sooner.
- Was kimura alone?
- Yes.
Where's Juliette?
How's she doing?
She's in the hospital.
What?
It had nothing
to do with kimura.
She's in a coma.
Something
to do with an infection.
They're still trying
to figure it out.
Look, Nick,
we've got this covered.
If you want to
go to the hospital...
- if my being there
would help her come out of this,
I wouldn't leave her side,
but there's nothing I can do.
They're gonna call me
when there's a change.
Well, at least
we got this son of a bitch.
Looks pretty quiet in there.
Cats don't, like, um,
play possum, do they?
Not with what I gave it.
Okay.
Ready.
Bring me the cat.
What's supposed to happen?
If it turns yellow,
I'll have a good idea
of what the toxin was
that infected Juliette.
If it turns green, there's still
a chance we can help her.
Hey, what about blue?
We have to talk to Nick now.
[Police radio chatter]
Hey.
Want me to leave
a few officers?
No, that's not necessary.
We've got kimura.
Well, get some rest.
Let me know if I can
do anything for Juliette.
- I will, thank you.
- All right.
I need to get to kimura.
Well, that's not
gonna be easy.
He's in police custody now.
But at least
he's not going anywhere.
You don't understand him.
I do. I've been following him
for a long time.
You didn't want to kill him
either, did you?
No.
I wanted to find out
why he killed my parents.
He's the last man alive
who knows who betrayed us.
So what, is my dad just gonna
come back from the dead too now?
No. He was killed
in the crash...
Which I guess you know
wasn't an accident.
The police thought
it was you who died in the car.
Who died in your place?
My friend.
Gina Serafini.
And why was she in the car?
On the night they came for me,
I didn't have much time.
You remember your aunt Marie
came to pick you up.
Yeah, I remember everything
from that night.
Well, Gina was staying
with us.
I sent her away
with your father,
thinking they'd get away
from whoever was after me,
but they didn't.
Why didn't the police identify
the bodies with dental records?
The killers thought
they'd killed a Grimm.
They took Gina's head.
The bodies were so badly burnt,
there was nothing else
to identify her with.
So you just
let me think you were dead?
It was the only way
I could think to protect you.
I have a lot of enemies, Nick.
Did aunt Marie
know you were alive?
Yes.
[Exhales sharply]
It was safer for you
if I was dead.
[Knocking at the door]
Stay back.
Hey,
we tried calling, but...
dude.
What the hell happened here?
Kimura.
Remember that guy
I was telling you about?
Oh, man, he's still here.
I can smell him.
That's not a him.
That's a her.
[Growls]
[Grunting and hissing]
Stop!
No!
Don't hurt him!
No! No!
No! No! No!
Do not hurt him!
- Stop, stop!
- His name is Monroe.
- He's a blutbad!
- Yeah,
and Rosalee's a fuchsbau.
They're both my friends.
Who the hell is this bitch?
Hey!
She's my mother.
Dude.
You told me she was...
I mean, isn't she supposed to
be, like, not so alive?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
I don't believe
what I'm hearing.
Are you friends with them?
And we're friends with him.
Yeah, it took a little getting
used to for us too, you know?
Did you know she was coming?
No.
Juliette
is in real danger, Nick,
and we don't have much time.
- Who's Juliette?
- Oh, wow, so you two
really haven't caught up
in any significant way, I guess.
Juliette's my girlfriend.
And she's in a coma
because of a hexenbiest.
The hexenbiest
that Nick destroyed
with our help, by the way,
just, you know, for the record.
Nick, the spell is called
l'esprit ailleurs.
Literall spirit elsewhere.
Oddly apropos.
It causes memory loss
with symptoms
similar to dementia.
So it's imperative
thate stop the progression,
like, asap.
Right now.
But we have
all the ingredients.
We have them mixed,
and they're cooking,
but it takes 16 hours
for it to be ready.
Well, will it bring her
out of the coma?
It's way more complicated.
Our first step is just
to stop the memory loss.
Okay, just do
whatever you have to do.
I'm just... I'm so sorry
this happened to Juliette.
And, uh... Sort of nice
to meet you.
Dude, I gotta be honest,
your mother
scares the crap out of me, man.
Look, you two should probably
just keep your distance
until I figure out
what I'm dealing with in there.
Yeah. No. Totally, I mean,
family reunions can be brutal.
Our last one, we lost
two cousins and a sheepdog.
- Okay.
- I mean,
no one missed the cousins,
you know, they're...
- this is Juliette.
She's very pretty.
How long
have you been together?
Where have you been
for 18 years?
More places
than I care to remember.
Why don't you try?
I went after
those responsible
for killing your father
and my friend.
For 18 years?
I had no idea
how long it would take
or where it would lead
or how many times
I'd be misled and deceived.
When I learned about the secret
order, the dragon's tongue,
that they were after the coins,
I knew there was more at stake
than just finding the killers.
I had to deal
with the royal families
who are trying
to regain the control
they had in the last century.
A lot of the turmoil
in the world today
is instigated by their agents.
Like the verrat.
You're learning.
That's good.
I wish I could have been
the one who taught you.
When I learned
that a Grimm had the coins,
I was hoping it wasn't you.
I often wonder how I could have
done things differently
that night, but...
Kimura led me to you,
and that's all that matters.
What about the coins?
They've already taken up
too much of our lives.
They need to be destroyed.
The sooner you give them
to me, the better.
It's the only way
I can protect you now.
[Knocking at door]
Where's adalind?
Why would you think
I know where she is?
You're her mother.
Well, that's a little
old-school, even for you.
She's gone.
She played
one last little trick.
She put Nick's girlfriend
in a coma.
And I care about that why?
Because it concerns me.
Can you really blame adalind
after what he did to her?
Yes!
She should stay out of things
that she does not understand.
Well, maybe you
played with her heart
a little too freely,
and that confused her.
No, she knew exactly
what she was doing.
Why do you care what happens
to detective Burkhardt's
girlfriend?
Because she ties him here...
To Portland, to me,
and if she dies, he could
quit the force, he could leave,
and I have put too much time
and effort into him
to allow that to happen.
Now, I need to know
what adalind did.
A Grimm on his own
is dangerous for all of us.
And I'm holding you
personally responsible,
and believe me,
you don't want that.
That's amazing...
based on a pair of boots
you could find out
where the guy lived.
Yeah. And his cabin
is way out there.
I don't think Nick could have
found it without me.
You went there with Nick?
I thought you went there
with Hank.
I did.
Yeah.
Nick?
[Roars]
Oh, crap, the toast.
I got it.
Thanks.
I was just trying to
make you a little...
Something.
[Cell phone ringing] I'm sorry.
For what?
A lot of things on that list.
Burkhardt.
Where?
On my way.
So I've got an investigation.
Gotta run.
You gonna be here
when I get back?
Yes.
Hey.
How you holding up?
All right.
It's gonna be okay, man.
Juliette's gonna
come out of it, she's strong.
Well, I hope you're right.
I am.
I may not be awake,
but I'm right.
Who's the ship registered to?
Holding company
based in Rotterdam.
Oh, it's a foreign ship.
The feds are gonna have
jurisdiction.
Have they been notified?
Yeah.
They're on their way.
Who reported it?
Harbor master
was called last night.
Three of them went inside.
Nobody came out.
Bodies weren't discovered
until 6:15 this morning
by one of the security guards.
He was pretty shook up
by what he saw,
and I gotta tell you,
this one is, uh...
Well, I hate to ruin
the surprise.
What the hell did this?
Something
out of my worst nightmare.
I don't think
this container was used
to lock anyone out.
It was used
to lock something in.
Found out the container was
loaded at le havre two weeks ago.
Name on the ship manifest
is G.Q.R. Industries.
Who are they,
and what do they do?
It looks like
a holding company.
We don't know much more
than that.
We contacted French police.
Waiting on a reply.
[Desk phone beeps]
Uhhuh.
Yeah?
Sir, the FBI agents are here.
Send 'em in.
You know the feds
are taking over this, right?
Sir, I think
that might be a mistake.
It's not up to us.
Just collect
whatever you've done,
pass it to them.
[Knocking]
Special agents
Kanigher and durwell,
this is captain renard,
detectives
Griffin and Burkhardt.
Hell of a mess
we're giving you.
Yeah, we just
came from down there.
You did a fine job
securing the location.
Yeah, we appreciate it.
What do you got for us?
All the prelim we could get.
Look, we might
be able to be of some help.
That's okay, detective,
we'll take it from here.
We've already got a line:
Security guard's truck
was stolen last night
from the docks.
If this killer's driving it,
we'll get him.
Well, I understand that,
there are aspects of this ca...
- hey, Nick.
Detective.
Thank you.
Gentlemen.
Here's how it's gonna go.
First thing tomorrow, you'll be
arraigned for double homicide.
A few hours after that,
you'll be transferred
to a maximum security facility,
ere you will await trial,
be found guilty,
and sentenced to death.
Now, obviously, I will derive
a certain amount
of pleasure from that,
seeing as I can't
attend to you myself.
Then maybe
you shouldn't have arrested me.
If I'd have
gotten to you first,
I wouldn't have.
Why are you here?
I've seen the tattoos
on your back.
I know who you're working for.
Too bad you didn't know you were
going up against a Grimm.
So you know what I am.
It would have been
better for you
had you known whatiam.
At least now I know
who has the coins.
I would have gotten them.
I knew there was one Grimm.
I didn't know there were two.
Mom?
I did a little cleaning up.
Sorry, habit.
Right.
- Hope it's okay.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
Hey, look. I've been thinking
about everything,
and...
I think I need to
take you somewhere.
I never thought
I'd see this again.
You know about this?
Marie and I
bought this trailer
when our dad got sick.
We needed
a place to hide everything
that had been
passed down to us.
We had 17 trunks hidden
in the basement of our house.
Who else in our family
had this...
Problem?
That I know of?
Your grandfather,
your great-grandmother,
and aunt Marie.
- And Uncle George had it too?
- No.
Not everyone does.
In fact, nobody knows
when it's gonna hit them
or even if they've got it.
Women become aware sooner
than men, but the only thing
we know for sure is
it's inherited.
There are a lot of people
who'd like to get their hands
on this stuff.
What did you think when
you first found out about...
You know, all of this?
I was only ten years old.
Your grandfather didn't even
try to protect me,
so as soon as the nightmares
started, he wanted me
to know exactly what I was
gonna be up against.
I was so scared,
I didn't sleep for months.
When I turned 18,
he took Marie and me
on the hunts.
The first couple
were horrifying,
but, uh, we quickly realized
that we were doing
what had to be done.
We spent hours
poring over these books.
[Inhales]
You know, I...
I never wanted this for you.
It's not as if
you had much of a choice.
Lot of history here.
Your great-great-grandmother
hilda, with this blade,
castrated a rotznasig carcaju.
[Blade sings into scabbard]
That's good times.
[Chuckles]
You know, this is all
very important to us.
Now what?
Uh...
Return them
to the island of zakynthos,
where they were forged.
It's the only way
to destroy them.
So I guess you'll be leaving.
You know what, I guess
I understand more now than...
look, you know, I have seen
a lot of things.
I mean, I cannot judge
the decisions
that you had to make.
But you know, I just wish
I didn't have to
grow up without you.
So do I.
[Sniffles]
Maybe you can help me.
What is it?
An investigation
I'm working on.
I want you to look at this.
Where is this?
A container on a cargo ship
that left le havre
two weeks ago.
Do you know
what the scythe means?
Yeah.
Reapers.
And you've dealt with one?
Actually,
I've dealt with three.
Was one of them French?
We didn't do
too much talking.
Then you were the one who
returned the heads to mannheim.
You know about that?
News travels fast.
No, I don't think
that is reapers.
No, no, no.
No, something else drew those.
And if it's
what I think it is...
It's worse than reapers.
I hope I'm wrong about this.
Were there any puncture wounds?
There were a lot of wounds.
We need to go.
Well, what about the coins?
Just put them away.
I need to see the bodies.
[Whip cracking, whimpering]
- [Grunts]
- Hold on.
[Coughing]
As you can see,
your friends in the resistance
aren't helping you,
so why are you helping them?
Hmm?
I personally hate to resort
to such medieval methods
and would much prefer
you join me for supper.
We're having
a very nice lafite,
and I'd like to toast
your health.
All you have to do
is give us their names,
and you will walk out of here.
Well, maybe crawl out now,
but at least you'll be out.
[Cell phone ringing]
Why don't you think about that
while I take this call?
Bonjour, mon ami.
How was the voyage?
[Speaking french]
Tres bien.I have seen him.
And?
It will be over soon.
The families
will be very pleased.
[Screams]
I amonthephone!
Is there anything else
that you need?
No.
I'll call you when it is done.
I'll look forward to it.
Can I help you?
I have a list.
I have everything except
for the pseudomonas aeruginosa.
I need it.
It might take me
a couple of days to...
- [roars]
Now would be better.
I'll see what I can do.
Give me a call
when you have it.
I'll give you my number.
This is the security guard,
and the killer stole his truck,
and I want to warn you,
it's a little rough.
Or not.
You know what this is?
Something with teeth
this big?
There's not a lot of choices.
Is it the...
- mauvais dentes.
From what our ancestors wrote,
it's a vicious killing machine.
One of them can wipe out
an entire village,
but you better be careful.
Mauvais dentes is like a cat.
He'll watch, he'll wait.
If he figures out
you're coming after him,
he'll do something
to draw you in.
[Cell phone ringing]
This is Monroe.
Yeah.
Hey, Nick.
It's me and rosalee.
We're in the shop.
Weird thing just happened.
I just got an order
from a hexenbiest.
And the few things on her list
are the same that we're using
for Juliette.
So we looked it up
in a couple of rosalee's books,
and we think we figured out
what she's doing.
It's a wake-up potion
for somebody
in Juliette's condition.
I mean, this could
just be a coincidence, but...
Totally.
We thought we should
tell you anyway.
Well, who was it?
I didn't get
a good look at her,
but rosalee got her number,
didn't you?
- Yeah.
- Okay, give it to me,
I can get her address
from her number.
- It's 503...
- It's 503-555-0138.
[Cell phone ringing]
- What did you find out?
- Adalind's gone,
I don't know where.
Obviously, she doesn't want
anybody to find her.
But there may be a way
to reverse
what she's done to Juliette.
Good. Then do it.
It's not the preparation
that concerns me.
It's how it's given to her.
What do you need?
Not "what."
Who.
What are you talking about?
How badly do you want to
wake this sleeping beauty up?
[Roars]
Right.
Hexenbiest.
Where's adalind?
I said, where's your daughter?
You're the Grimm
who destroyed her.
And I'm the Grimm
who's gonna destroy you
if you don't tell me
where she is.
I don't know.
We haven't spoken
since that night.
Don't you need a warrant
to be doing this, detective?
If I was here as a cop, yeah.
She is not here.
I have no reason
to protect her anymore.
Well, then find her,
or things are gonna get a little
dangerous here for you.
Are you threatening me?
I'm sorry.
I must have done it badly.
I thought I made myself
pretty obvious.
If Juliette dies...
You're done.
She said she doesn't know
where adalind is.
Did you threaten to kill her?
Yeah, of course.
Want me to take a crack
at her?
No, she's telling me
the truth.
I didn't think that was
possible for a hexenbiest.
Was she involved
in trying to kill aunt Marie?
Not that I know of.
The only person I saw
was adalind.
Why would she
try to kill her?
I don't know.
What?
Before she died,
did aunt Marie
give you anything?
Yeah.
A key.
I have no idea what it's for,
it doesn't open anything
in the trailer, but...
The sides of it make a...
Map.
Where is it?
[Speaking French]
I only discovered
these by accident
when I spilled some ink.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Oh, damn!
Okay, that was cool.
What is that?
A page from one of the first
diaries ever kept by one of us.
You see, legend has it
that there are seven keys.
Seven?
Forged by the knights
who fought
for the seven royal families
in the fourth crusade.
Now, when you put the maps
together,
they make one big map,
leading to the location
where the knights hid
the precious wealth
they took from constantinople
after they sacked
and burned it.
Those knights
are our ancestors.
Whatso they worked
for the seven royal families.
Some of them did.
Well, they needed us.
So the wesen
fought for the royals?
Yes, and the royals needed
the grimms to control them,
as they do now, but there was
one thing in the treasure
the knights hid.
There was one thing
that was more powerful
than anything
anyone had ever seen.
If the royal families
got ahold of it,
they could control the world.
Okay, so nothing really big.
I guess they hid this thing
pretty well?
Sure, yeah.
They made a map,
they cut it into seven pieces,
and they gave each knight
a key.
- What was so powerful?
- I wish I knew.
This is the only page left
of the diary.
The rest was destroyed
in the wesen wars of 1285.
Okay, now I have a headache.
Nick...
They know you have the key.
- Who?
- The royal families.
They're the only ones
powerful enough
to send the mauvais dentes.
Now my guess is,
they want the key,
and they want you dead.
[Chuckles] How would
they know I have a key?
I haven't shown it to anyone.
There must be somebody
in Portland who knows.
I think we have
to get to kimura
because he might give us
the connection.
We need to talk to him.
You cannot go
to the precinct.
No, but you can.
[Chuckles]
Food.
[ Music playing ]
[Gags]
[Chokes]
Argh!
This is
special agent Kanigher.
I have information about
the case you're working on.
The security guard's stolen
pickup truck you're looking for
is at the lumber mill
on St. Helen's road.
Who is this?
A concerned citizen.
There's the truck.
Just where he said
it would be.
Is he in the vehicle?
- No.
- I see him. He's inside.
FBI!
Get over here!
I am the one who called you.
What are you doing in here?
Waiting for you.
Take out your identification.
I'm sorry, I don't have any.
Put your hands on your head.
Turn around.
D'accord.
[Grunts]
[Speaking French]
[Growling]
[Screams]
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Guards! Come on, open this cell!
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Guards, move!
What happened?
Kimura's dead.
In police custody?
Somebody got to him.
[Cell phone ringing]
Burkhardt.
Detective,
it's agent Kanigher.
What's wrong?
I'm in the old lumber mill
out on St. Helen's road.
I know it.
What do you need?
He killed my partner.
He said if you don't come,
alone, he's gonna kill me.
Detective, he's gonna...
[Whimpers]
The mauvais dentes
killed an FBI agent.
He's got another,
waiting for me.
He's drawing you in.
Let's not keep him waiting.
He's got the agents
inside the building.
That doesn't mean
he'll be there.
He'll want you to get close.
I don't know how,
but he will try to deceive you.
He won't be predictable.
[Cell phone ringing]
- [Whispering] Yeah?
- Nick,
we got the stuff
for Juliette, okay?
It's ready, but it's, like,
unstable or something,
and it's only gonna be good
for, like...
- another 45 more minutes,
give or take,
and if we don't make it,
we have to start from scratch.
Just meet us at the hospital,
okay?
We're leaving right now.
I'll be there
as soon as I can.
Nick, what's wrong?
Can't get into it right now.
[Growls]
[Roars]
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.Com
www.tvsubtitles.net